

My Contact



muralidk0819@gmail.com



+91-7397568984



29, Vishnupriya Garden, Tirupur- 06.



https://www.linkedin.com/in/muralikrishnan-601752225

Hard Skill

- Website Designing
- Search Engine Marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Keyword Research
- Paid Marketing
- Lead Generations
- Email Marketing

Soft Skill

- Team Work & Team Leadership
- Innovative Thinking
- Leadership & Mentorship

Education Background

- Hindustan College of Arts and Science
 Bachelor of Commerce with Computer
 Science Distinction with 71% Completed in 2020
- Vidhya Vikashni matric.Hr.Sec.School
 SSLC Destinction with 86% Completed in 2017
- Vidhya Vikashni matric.Hr.Sec.School
 SSLC Destinction with 83% Completed in 2015

Internship Program

Digital Marketing Intern - SGS Mediasoft

- Handling Client's Website Blog Management
- Help the digital marketing team set up fan engagement campaigns, redesign websites, update websites, determine keywords, provide customer service online, perform a cost-benefit analysis, post content, and check web content.

<u> Murali Krishnan . D</u>

Seo Specialist

About Me

Dedicated Digital Marketer with 8 Months of experience in Web designing, Keyword Research, and Building paid and Organic marketing to bring leads or Traffic to the Website. My strengths include growing audiences and increasing engagement; developing successful On-Page SEO and Off-Page SEO setting up; managing and implementing effective content strategies

Professional Experience

Focus Edumatrics | Math Online Tutor Jan 2020 – April 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Providing students with a better understanding of how to solve problems and guiding them to solve the problem step by step
- Monitoring student activity in class and providing guidance in course development
- constructed and rebuilt lessons according to dynamic interests and current events.

Hashtag Infosystem | Email Marketing &B2B Lead Generation

April 2021- December 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Research, track, maintain, and update leads.
- Conduct customer research based on a specific niche.
- · Direct email marketing to key clients and prospects

Traffic Crow | Digital Marketing Team Head

January 2022 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Analyzed SEO outreach objectives and reported findings to marketing director.
- recommended changes to website architecture, content, and links to improve SEO positions for target keywords.
- measured and reported the performance of all digital marketing campaigns, and assessed them against ROI and KPIs.
- tracked, reported, and analysed website analytics to drive strategy and improve the user experience.

Achievements and Certifications

2017 Course on Diploma in Digital Finance (DDF) afflicted by Bharathidasan University in Hindusthan College of Arts and Science

2022 Certification of professional Achievement in Digital Marketing in Sgs Mediasoft